COME ON, JOEY.
I TOLD YOU EVERYTHING
I KNEW LAST NIGHT.
IT'S NOT THAT BIG A DEAL.
SO MONICA AND CHANDLER
ARE DOING IT.
I CANNOT BELIEVE
YOU WOULD SAY THAT.
SORRY. MONICA AND CHANDLER
ARE "MAKING LOVE."
NO, I MEAN, COME ON
THIS IS A HUGE DEAL.
COME ON, I NEED
MORE DETAILS.
LIKE, WHO INITIATED
THE FIRST KISS?
I DON'T KNOW.
IS HE ROMANTIC
WITH HER?
I DON'T KNOW.
ARE THEY IN LOVE?
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
OH, I KNOW ONE THING.
WHAT?
THEY DID IT RIGHT THERE
ON THE COUCH
YESTERDAY.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY, ROSS.
HEY.
YEAH.
HEY, GUNTHER,
COULD I HAVE
A SCONE, PLEASE?
WANT TO HEAR SOME GOOD NEWS?
SOMEONE I KNOW
IS GETTING MARRIED.
YEAH, AND WEDDINGS
ARE HAPPY OCCASIONS.
OH, BY-THE-BY,
IT'S MY EX-WIFE, EMILY.
( all gasp )
I'M SORRY, MAN.
HERE'S YOUR SCONE.
THANKS, GUNTHER.
THANKS.
STUPID BRITISH SNACK FOOD!
DID THEY
TEACH YOU THAT
IN YOUR ANGER
MANAGEMENT CLASS?
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT
MIGHT HELP YOU DEAL WITH IT?
THINK OF IT THIS WAY...
YOU AND EMILY ARE IN THE PAST.
AND YOU CAN'T BE MAD
ABOUT THE PAST.
ARE YOU STILL MAD
ABOUT THE LOUISIANA PURCHASE?
I DON'T THINK
ANYBODY'S MAD
ABOUT THAT.
EXACTLY, BECAUSE
IT'S IN THE PAST.
ANYBODY
GOING TO EAT THAT?
LOOK AT US,
ALL DRESSED UP
FOR THE BIG
OFFICE PARTY.
WHAT ARE WE
CELEBRATING?
WE HAD LIQUOR LEFT OVER
FROM THE CHRISTMAS PARTY.
I THINK THIS
IS SO COOL.
NONE OF OUR FRIENDS
ARE HERE
SO WE CAN BE
A REAL COUPLE
WE DON'T
HAVE TO HIDE.
I KNOW,
I CAN DO THIS.
OOH.
AND I CAN DO THIS.
Both:
WE CAN'T DO THAT, NO.
HEY, BING.
WHOA...
WHO'S THE PRETTY LADY
AND WHAT THE HELL
IS SHE DOING WITH YOU?
I ASK MYSELF
THAT VERY QUESTION, SIR.
THIS IS MONICA.
THIS IS
MY BOSS, DOUG.
DOUG, THIS IS MONICA.
NICE TO
MEET YOU.
HI, THIS IS
MY WIFE, KARA.
NICE TO MEET
YOU, MONICA.
BING!
OKAY.
HEY, BING, DID YOU HEAR
ABOUT THE NEW LAW FIRM
WE GOT WORKING FOR US?
NO, SIR.
YEAH, DEWEY, CHEATEM
& HOWE.
( forced laugh )
COME ON, HONEY
LET'S GO DRINK
OUR BODY WEIGHT, HUH?
WHAT WAS THAT?
WHAT?
THAT NOISE
YOU JUST MADE.
OH, THAT WAS
MY WORK LAUGH.
REALLY?
YOUR WORK LAUGH?
BELIEVE ME, IF YOU'RE GOING
TO SURVIVE THIS PARTY
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO COME UP WITH ONE, TOO.
ALL RIGHT,
CHECK ME OUT.
OKAY.
...HE SAYS, "$30, FATHER,
SAME AS IN TOWN."
( high pitched laugh )
HEY, EVERYBODY AT WORK,
LOVED YOU LAST NIGHT.
REALLY?
AND THEY LIKE ME MORE
JUST BECAUSE
I WAS WITH YOU.
I THINK YOU REPAIRED
A LOT OF THE DAMAGE
FROM WHEN THEY MET JOEY.
AND DOUG WANTS US
TO PLAY TENNIS WITH HIM.
HE'S NEVER EVEN
TALKED TO ME
OUTSIDE OF WORK.
EXCEPT FOR THAT
TIME WHEN WE BUMPED
INTO EACH OTHER
AT THAT STRIP CLUB.
STRIP... CHURCH.
ANYWAY, I'M GOING
TO GO TRY TO
FIND A RACKET.
I THOUGHT YOU HAD ONE.
OH, I USED TO
BUT THEN JOEY THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE FUN
TO GO TO CENTRAL PARK
AND HIT ROCKS
AT BIGGER ROCKS.
HEY, RACH,
DO YOU HAVE A TENNIS RACKET?
OH, I LENT IT TO JOEY
AND I'VE NEVER ACTUALLY
GOTTEN IT BACK.
OKAY, GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT YOU HAD TO DO
INVENTORY ALL DAY.
WELL, YEAH, I DO.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I DECIDED
I WOULD TAKE A LONG LUNCH
AND SPEND SOME TIME
WITH MY FRIEND, MONICA.
YOU KNOW, I FEEL LIKE
WE DON'T TALK ANYMORE.
HOW ARE YOU?
WHAT IS
NEW WITH YOU?
UM, NOT MUCH.
UH... WORK'S GOOD.
OH, YOU KNOW, WE DON'T
HAVE TO TALK ABOUT WORK.
WE CAN TALK
ABOUT ANYTHING.
OKAY, UM...
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S TALK ABOUT
RELATIONSHIPS.
OKAY, WHAT'S
GOING ON WITH YOU?
NOTHING.
YOU GO.
WELL, THERE WAS THIS GUY
AT THE BANK
THAT I THOUGHT WAS CUTE.
UM, BUT I DON'T ANYMORE.
WOW, THAT'S JUICY.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
THOUGH, MON?
I ACTUALLY DO
HAVE A LOT OF
WORK TO DO.
SO, IF YOU'RE SURE THERE'S
JUST NOT ANYTHING ELSE...?
YES, I'M SURE.
RACHEL,
IS THERE SOMETHING
THAT YOU WANT
TO TALK TO ME ABOUT?
( sharply ):
NO.
I...
IF THERE WAS,
I WOULDN'T TELL YOU.
( duck quacking )
OKAY, THEN WHAT HAPPENED?
OH...
UH-HUH, UH-HUH.
( chicken clucks )
YOU'LL GET YOUR TURN.
HEY, PHEEBS.
HEY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
NOTHING.
THIS IS NOT OVER.
NO, NO, NO.
WHAT?
I WAS UP ALL NIGHT
WRITING THIS REALLY
NASTY LETTER TO EMILY.
IT WAS PERFECT.
AND NOW IT'S ALL COVERED IN...
ACTUALLY, THANKS.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY
READY TO GO TO THE MOVIES?
UH, ACTUALLY I THINK
I'M GOING TO SKIP IT.
REALLY?
YEAH, I'M GOING
TO STAY AND
READ MY BOOK.
I JUST WANT TO
BE ALONE RIGHT NOW.
OH, SURE YOU
DON'T WANT TO COME?
TOM HANKS, MEG RYAN...
THEY GET MAIL AND STUFF.
THAT'S OKAY, JOE.
ALL RIGHT.
( duck quacking )
OOH... OH, GOD.
BING.
( screams )
GAME.
WELL, I GOT TO
TELL YOU, BING.
THAT PARTNER OF YOURS
IS A REAL TIGER.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
SWEETHEART?
WE'RE JUST GOING TO GET
A LITTLE SIP OF WATER.
AM I ON FIRE TODAY,
OR WHAT?
THOSE BIRDS ARE BROWN, BASTED
AND READY TO BE CARVED.
OKAY... EASY, MARTINA.
LISTEN, I THINK WE SHOULD
LET THEM WIN THE NEXT GAME.
I'M SORRY, I DON'T
UNDERSTAND WHAT
YOU JUST SAID.
LET THEM WIN ONE.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
WE OWN THOSE TWO.
LOOK AT THEM.
HE CAN'T EVEN BREATHE
AND SHE'S POPPIN' PILLS.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN
GIVING THEM A CHANCE.
THEY HAVE RACKETS,
DON'T THEY?
UH, BING, I THINK WE'RE
GOING TO MAKE THIS
THE LAST GAME.
OH, YES, SIR.
PUT ME
OUT OF MY MISERY.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU NEVER PLAYED PRO?
PLEASE LET THEM WIN.
I'LL TAKE IT
DOWN TO 95%
BUT THAT'S THE BEST
I CAN DO.
OOPSEY, MISSED IT.
I GOT IT.
NICE SHOT.
LONG.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU LET THEM WIN.
YEAH, AT LEAST YOU HID
YOUR FEELINGS WELL ABOUT IT.
I WAS FRUSTRATED.
IT WAS MY RACKET.
I WAS FRUSTRATED
WITH YOU.
IF WE HADN'T
LOST THE GAME
THEY WOULD NEVER
HAVE INVITED US
TO DINNER TOMORROW NIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT
REALLY BOTHERS ME?
IT'S HOW DIFFERENT
YOU ACT AROUND THEM.
I MEAN, THE THROWING
THE TENNIS GAMES
THE FAKE LAUGH,
THE "SEE YA
LATER, BING."
"NOT IF I SEE
YOU FIRST, DOUG."
"AH, AH, AH, AH!"
I GOT TO TELL YOU
I DON'T LIKE
"WORK CHANDLER."
THE GUY'S A SUCK-UP.
OKAY, BECAUSE
YOU SAID THAT
I'M NOT
PUTTING OUT TONIGHT.
I'M TELLING YOU,
SOMETHING'S WRONG.
MY BROTHER DOES NOT
STAY OUT ALL NIGHT.
MAYBE WE SHOULD CHECK
THE TRASH CHUTE.
ROSS COULDN'T FIT
DOWN THE TRASH CHUTE.
THAT'S RIGHT, HE ALMOST COULD.
WHICH IS EXACTLY
HOW I GOT STUCK THERE.
HEY.
OH, MY GOD.
WHERE THE HELL
HAVE YOU BEEN?
JUST...
YOU KNOW, OUT.
OH... OUT.
OH, GOD,
I DON'T KNOW WHY
WE DIDN'T THINK
TO CHECK THERE.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING?
I, UH...
WENT TO A BAR.
AND THEN I JUST WALKED AROUND
FOR A WHILE.
YOU WALK AROUND
ALL NIGHT
IN THE CITY
BY YOURSELF?
HE HOOKED UP.
HE HOOKED UP
WITH SOMEONE.
LOOK, I DON'T HAVE TO ANSWER
YOUR QUESTIONS, OKAY?
I'M A BIG BOY.
I CAN DO WHATEVER I WANT.
HE HOOKED UP.
TELL US ABOUT HER.
ROSS, YOU LET YOUR SCARF IN...
HEY, YOU GUYS.
( horselike giggles )
O-O-OKAY. OKAY.
I KNOW WHAT YOU ALL
ARE THINKING
BUT CHANDLER IS IN YEMEN.
I'M A YOUNG WOMAN.
I HAVE NEEDS.
I CAN'T WAIT FOREVER.
YEAH, NO, THAT'S
WHAT I WAS THINKING.
SO I'M ASKING YOU, PLEASE
JUST TAKE A MOMENT
BEFORE YOU JUDGE ME.
OH, NOBODY'S
JUDGING YOU.
OH. OKAY.
YOU, MR. "RIGHT PLACE
AT THE RIGHT TIME..."
CALL ME.
( braying laughter )
OKAY, LOOK, I KNOW
WHAT YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO SAY.
YOU TWO WOULD HAVE
VERY HAIRY CHILDREN.
OKAY, I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WOULD SAY THAT.
ROSS? JANICE?
ALL RIGHT, HOLD ON.
HOLD ON. HOLD ON.
THIS IS ROSS.
OKAY?
HE'S OUR FRIEND.
HE OBVIOUSLY
WENT CRAZY.
LOST HIS MIND.
NO, I DIDN'T LOSE MY MIND.
OKAY? JANICE AND I
HAVE A LOT IN COMMON.
WE'VE...
WE'VE BOTH BEEN DIVORCED.
WE... WE BOTH HAVE KIDS.
SO ARE YOU ACTUALLY
GOING TO SEE HER AGAIN?
PHOEBE, DON'T PUT
IDEAS IN HIS HEAD.
I AM GOING
TO SEE HER AGAIN.
DAMN IT, PHOEBE!
OKAY, I HAVE
TO TELL YOU SOMETHING
THAT I'VE NEVER ADMITTED
THROUGHOUT OUR ENTIRE FRIENDSHIP
BUT WHEN WE WERE
IN HIGH SCHOOL
I MADE OUT
WITH JAMES FARROW
EVEN THOUGH I KNEW
THAT YOU LIKED HIM.
WOW, THAT FEELS SO GOOD
TO GET OFF MY CHEST.
OKAY, YOU GO.
MY TURN?
W-WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
MONICA... I KNOW
ABOUT YOU AND CHANDLER.
WHAT?
I OVERHEARD YOU GUYS
ON THE PHONE THE OTHER DAY
AND YOU SAID,
"I'LL JUST TELL RACHEL
THAT I'M DOING LAUNDRY
FOR A COUPLE OF HOURS."
AND HE SAID, "LAUNDRY?
"IS THAT MY NEW NICKNAME?"
AND YOU SAID, "NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOUR NICKNAME IS,
MR. BIG."
WELL... SOUNDS LIKE
YOU'RE WRITING YOURSELF
A LITTLE PLAY
THERE, RACH.
WOW, I... LET ME KNOW
HOW THAT ONE TURNS OUT.
WELL, I WOULDN'T KNOW
BECAUSE I GOT SO FREAKED OUT
I HUNG UP THE PHONE.
WELL, IF YOU HAD
KEPT LISTENING
Y-YOU WOULD HAVE HEARD
ME CALL HIM MR. BIG... IT.
WHAT?
MR. BIGOT.
I MEAN....
HE TELLS THE
MOST RACIST JOKES.
ALL RIGHT. SO THAT'S IT?
YOU'RE TELLING ME
THERE'S NOTHING GOING ON
BETWEEN YOU AND CHANDLER?
ME AND CHANDLER?
( work laughter )
ALL RIGHT, PUT
YOUR 20 BUCKS DOWN.
FIRST ONE TO FIND THE
TASTY TREAT WINS. OKAY?
MM-HMM.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET THE CONTESTANTS
OUT OF THEIR ISOLATION BOOTHS.
AND THEY'RE OFF.
OH...
GET YOUR FOOT OFF
MY CONTESTANT. JUDGE?
JUDGE RULES
NO VIOLATION.
( sighing )
HEY, GUYS.
HEY.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S SO WEIRD TO SAY THIS
BUT I JUST HAD
A GREAT DATE WITH JANICE.
WHAT?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YEAH. I OPENED UP TO HER
ABOUT ALL THE TERRIBLE STUFF
THAT'S BEEN HAPPENING TO ME.
I MEAN, I TALKED FOR HOURS.
IT IS AMAZING
TO HAVE SOMEONE GIVE YOU
SUCH... SUCH FOCUSED ATTENTION.
YOU DON'T NEED
JANICE FOR THAT.
YOU'VE GOT US.
THE DUCK GETS
A NUTTER BUTTER.
EEW! OH, HEY,
THAT'S NOT
A NUTTER BUTTER.
THAT'S JUST
AN OLD WONTON.
JUDGE RULES...
NUTTER BUTTER.
( groaning )
TOUGH CALL.
YEAH.
( laughter )
BUT, SERIOUSLY,
I STRONGLY BELIEVE
THAT WE SHOULD ALL SUPPORT
PRESIDENT CLINTON
AND HER HUSBAND, BILL.
( guys laughing obnoxiously )
SO, HOW DO YOU KIDS
LIKE YOUR COFFEE?
OH, NONE FOR
ME, THANKS.
A LITTLE BIT
OF SUGAR.
I'LL BRING IT OUT
AND HAVE MONICA
STICK HER FINGER IN IT.
THAT'LL SWEETEN IT UP.
( guys laughing )
HOW DOES THAT LAUGH
NOT GIVE YOU A HEADACHE?
OH, YOU GET USED TO IT.
I-I DON'T THINK
THAT I CAN
SO, IF YOU DON'T MIND
MAYBE THIS WILL BE IT
FOR ME ON THE WORK THINGS.
SO I LAUGH AT MY BOSS'S JOKES.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
I'D RATHER NOT HANG OUT
WITH THIS SNIVELING,
WORK-WEASEL GUY
WHEN I COULD BE HANGING
OUT WITH MY BOYFRIEND,
WHO I ACTUALLY RESPECT.
OH.
AH. I GOT TO APOLOGIZE
FOR KARA'S COFFEE, YOU KNOW?
FEEL SORRY FOR IT
IF IT EVER GOT IN A FIGHT.
IT'S NOT STRONG ENOUGH
TO DEFEND ITSELF.
( laughing )
( laughter
tapers off )
DID YOU HEAR WHAT I SAID, BING?
WHAT?
IT'S A JOKE, BING.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
WELL, I-I, I JUST DIDN'T THINK
IT WAS FUNNY, SIR.
EXCUSE ME?
WELL, I-I JUST...
HONEY, I JUST DON'T
THINK THAT YOU
UNDERSTOOD THE JOKE.
REALLY?
YEAH. I MEAN...
IT WAS REALLY FUNNY.
I JUST DON'T THINK
THAT YOU GOT IT.
YOU SEE, KARA'S COFFEE
IS, IS, IS WEAK TASTING
OKAY, BUT WHAT DOUG
DID WAS TO IMPLY
THAT IT WAS WEAK
PHYSICALLY.
YOU GET IT
NOW, HONEY?
I THINK I DO.
( both laughing obnoxiously )
( Doug joins in )
THANK YOU, MONICA.
I THOUGHT YOU COULD
USE THE HELP.
COFFEE IN A FIGHT!
( both laughing )
HEY, RACH.
DO YOU MIND IF I READ
MY COMIC BOOKS IN HERE?
SURE. WHY?
OH, WELL
CHANDLER AND MONICA
ARE OVER THERE
AND, YOU KNOW, IT'S KIND OF HARD
TO CONCENTRATE.
WHAT?! SHE JUST CALLED
AND SAID THAT SHE WAS GOING
TO BE WORKING LATE.
OKAY, SHE KEEPS LYING
TO ME.
THAT'S IT. YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO GO OVER THERE
AND I'M CONFRONTING THEM
RIGHT NOW.
Chandler:
ALL RIGHT,
SO YOU'RE TELLING ME
THAT I HAVE TO TELL
RACIST JOKES NOW?
Monica:
I'M SORRY.
I'M NOT VERY GOOD AT THIS.
I'M A TERRIBLE LIAR
AND I HATE HAVING
TO LIE TO RACHEL.
YEAH, BUT WE'RE NOT READY
TO TELL YET.
I KNOW. IT'S JUST THAT
EVER SINCE HIGH SCHOOL,
RACHEL WAS THE ONE PERSON
THAT I TOLD
EVERYTHING
TO, YOU KNOW?
I MISS THAT
SO MUCH NOW.
SHE'S MY BEST FRIEND.
( gasping )
JOEY?
OH, MY GOD. RACHEL.
HEY! HI!
W-W-W-WHAT,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WELL, I WAS ACTUALLY...
I CAME OVER HERE
TO BORROW THIS LAMP...
TO, UM, LOOK AT MY BOOKS,
YOU KNOW?
SEE 'EM A LITTLE BETTER.
OKAY, GREAT. GREAT. UM...
W-WHAT I WAS DOING
IN CHANDLER'S ROOM
IS THAT, UM, WELL,
I WAS CLEANING IT.
OH.
IN FACT, HE PAYS ME TO CLEAN IT.
OH! WHAT A, YOU KNOW, GREAT WAY
TO MAKE SOME EXTRA POCKET MONEY.
YEAH. YOU KNOW,
WHEN I SAID TO YOU EARLIER
THAT I WAS AT WORK, UM...
I'M AT MY NEW WORK.
GOOD ENOUGH. RIGHT?
OKAY, WELL, UM...
I'M GOING
TO GO LOOK AT MY BOOKS.
OKAY.
GO GET BACK TO MY NEW JOB.
CONGRATULATIONS
ON YOUR NEW JOB.
( door opens
and shuts )
MAN, SHE IS
REALLY GULLIBLE.
( whistling )
HERE YOU GO.
OH, THANKS.
ACTUALLY, I
SHOULD GET GOING.
OH, Y-YOU SURE?
BECAUSE I CAN STAY OUT
AS LATE AS YOU WANT.
I TOLD YOU HOW I'M ON SABBATICAL
FROM WORK, RIGHT?
YES, YES, YOU DID.
( laughing )
( whining ):
OH, MAN!
WHAT IS WRONG NOW?
THIS ISN'T WHAT I ORDERED!
MAN, CAN'T ANYTHING
GO RIGHT IN MY LIFE?!
FIRST MY MARRIAGE FALLS APART,
AND THEN I...
I KNOW, I KNOW!
AND THEN YOU LOSE
YOUR APARTMENT
AND THEN YOU LOSE YOUR JOB
AND THEN YOUR EX-WIFE
GETS MARRIED SO FAST
AND NOW THE COFFEE... AAH!
ROSS.
WE NEED TO TALK.
OKAY.
SOMETIMES I FEEL...
NO-NO-NO-NO, NO, NO.
I'M GOING TO TALK.
I BELIEVE THAT THE
SUN HAS SET ON OUR...
DAY IN THE SUN.
WHAT?
YOU'RE A VERY SWEET
PERSON, ROSS... UM...
UNFORTUNATELY, I
JUST DON'T THINK
I CAN TAKE ANOTHER
SECOND OF YOU WHINING!
UH, LET ME MAKE SURE
I'M HEARING THIS RIGHT. YOU...
YOU'RE ENDING THIS WITH ME
BECAUSE I'M TOO WHINY?
MMM.
SO, YOU'RE SAYING
I'VE BECOME SO WHINY
THAT I
ANNOY YOU.
JANICE.
WELL, YEAH!
OH. MY. GOD.
ARE YOU GOING TO BE OKAY?
I AM NOW.
OKAY.
UH... HI.
OH, HI.
WELL...
I GUESS
THAT'S TWO OUT OF THREE.
JOEY.
( braying laugh )
DUDE, WE GOT TO TALK.
OKAY.
I JUST WANTED TO
TELL YOU SOMETHING
BEFORE YOU HEARD IT
FROM SOMEONE ELSE
AND I HOPE THIS
ISN'T TOO WEIRD
BUT, UH...
I HAD A-A THING WITH JANICE.
( cracking up )
WHAT, YOU'RE, YOU'RE NOT MAD?
WHY WOULD I BE MAD?
WELL, BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
THERE ARE CERTAIN RULES
ABOUT THIS KIND OF STUFF.
YOU DON'T, UH,
YOU DON'T FOOL AROUND
WITH YOUR FRIENDS'
EX-GIRLFRIENDS
OR, UH
POSSIBLE GIRLFRIENDS,
OR GIRLS THEY'RE RELATED TO.
I AM MAD.
BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M GONNA DO?
I'M GONNA FORGIVE YOU,
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT FRIENDS DO.
THEY FORGIVE THEIR FRIENDS
WHEN THEY DO
EVERYTHING YOU JUST SAID.
ALL THE THINGS
ON THE LIST THERE.
THANK YOU.
WELL
BUT I WANT YOU TO REMEMBER
THAT I FORGAVE YOU.
OKAY.
I ALSO WANT YOU TO REMEMBER
THAT I LET YOU LIVE HERE
RENT FREE.
ALL RIGHT.
AND I WANT YOU TO REMEMBER
THAT I GAVE YOU $27.
NO STRINGS ATTACHED.
IF YOU CAN'T
REMEMBER THAT
I THINK WE SHOULD WRITE IT DOWN.
LET'S WRITE IT DOWN.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]